RESUME

BEENITA BHATT

Computer Teacher

Phone no.- 9410553215 7817905283

Email- <u>beenitabhatt1112@gmail.com</u> Address- Pilikothi, Bari mukhani, Haldwani

SUMMARY

8 years of experience as a computer teacher. Achieving the post of computer teacher in an organization that will offer me to use my technical as well as intellectual abilities to contribute towards the organizational goals in consonance with its vision and policies, while being resourceful and innovative.

SKILL

Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Computer IT, Microsoft Office, HTML, Python, C++, C, SQL

WORK EXPERIENCE

Computer Teacher

Don Bosco Sr. Sec. School:- April 2015 - Present

- Conducting classes, labs and other computer related activities for students of class 6th to class 12th.
- Conducting training for staff and teachers about the basics of computers/internet.
- Guiding the children for all the computer project related presentation for inter school competition.
- Making teachers and class time table, and arrangement's of the teachers.
- All CBSE work of making official letters and query replies for cbse.
- Organizing the functions and Olympiads in campus.

Office executive

Brij lal hospital & research center:- July 2011 to march 2012

- Maintaining the attendance of the employees.
- Making covering letters of the TPA.
- Maintaining the personal data of the employees.

Computer Faculty

Aptech Institute: - July 2010 to June 2011

- Maintaining the fee record of the students.
- Teaching as a computer faculty in institute.

EDUCATION

- Professional qualification
 - 1 year Client Server Programming course from Aptech.
 - O level course from Doaecc.
 - D.EL.ED from NIOS.
 - CCC course from NEILTS.
 - Pursuing 6 semester of MCA from IGNOU, Haldwani.
- Academic qualification
 - B.A from kumaun university.
 - M.A in English from UOU.

PERSONAL SKILL

Determination, Courage, Friendship, Excellence, Inspiration

PERSONAL DETAIL

- Fathers Name:- Mr Jagdeesh Chandra Bhatt
- Mothers name:- Ms Deepa Bhatt
- ➤ DOB:- 28/08/1987

	Language	known:-	English	and Hindi
_	Language	KIIO WIII.	LIIGHSH	ana mia

(Beenita Bhatt)